#### Remove Watermark Nov

# AMY +6751124548 AMIAS@HOLOLO.COM

## **PROFILE**

Fund accountant with nearly 2 years of experience in hedge fund administration, which includes preparation of NAV calculations, financial statements and associated reports. Consistently meeting deadlines while ensuring a high quality of work standards. Fast learner, driven for results and analytical in problem solving.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Citco Fund Services (Singapore) Pte Ltd

Jan 2016 - Present Fund

Accountant

- Calculation of estimate and final NAVs on a daily, weekly and monthly basis
- Preparation of cash and position reconciliation reports
- Daily pre-production tasks such as price checks, interest accruals and fees booking
- Maintaining day-to-day relationships with investment managers, brokers and auditors
- Communicating with the reconciliations team to ensure consistent and high-quality standards when delivering NAV packages
- Undertaking fund migrations from Citco Toronto and Citco Dublin Office
- Familiar with various pricing valuation models e.g. Independent Price Verification, External Valuer
- Investigation and resolution of breaks
- Training of new fund accountants in the team
- Assist in reviewing estimate and final NAV packs

#### **Norgas Carriers Private Limited**

Nov 2014 - Apr 2015

Accountant

- Processing invoices from suppliers and scheduling payment remittances
- · Assisted in collecting outstanding debts from debtors
- · Involved in the year end closing of accounts
- Liaised with external auditors during interim and final audit
- Monthly bank reconciliation
- Perform intercompany journal entries and reconciliation

#### **Singapore Armed Forces**

Jul 2013 - July 2014 Operation

Specialist/ NSF Battery Sergeant Major (2<sup>nd</sup> Sergeant, 24<sup>th</sup> Battalion Singapore Artillery)

- In charge of the training management and administration matters, ensuring smooth running and operation of the battalion
- Responsible for the welfare, discipline and regimentation of 60 fellow NSFs
- Rallied with superiors to keep a lookout for troubled soldiers, acted as the first level of feedback for peers

## **EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS**

Royal Melbourne Institute of Technology (RMIT)

Jul 2014 - Oct 2015

Bachelor of Business (Accountancy)

GPA: 3.1 / 4

**Temasek Polytechnic** Apr 2009 - Apr 2012

Diploma in Accounting and Finance

**Ngee Ann Secondary School** Jan 2005 - Nov 2008

GCE 'O' Levels Certificate

## **SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES**

- Trained in accounting softwares, Aexeo, Agresso Business World, Sage AccPac and MYOB
- · Proficient in Microsoft Excel, PowerPoint and Word
- Competent in Financial and Economic Databases (Bloomberg, Thomson Reuters)
- Languages spoken: English, Chinese, Cantonese
- · Languages written: English, Chinese

